sulia.com 2012-11-05

# Sulia Privacy Policy

We at Sulia take your privacy very seriously. This Privacy Policy covers the treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personally Identifiable Information”) that you provide to us and that is gathered and shared when you are using or accessing Sulia.  Please read this notice carefully. 

If you have any questions on this policy, please contact us at [support@sulia.com](mailto:support@sulia.com)

## What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?

This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that we do not own or control, including but not limited to any third party websites, content sources, services and applications (“Third Party Services”) that you elect to access through Sulia, or to individuals that we do not manage or employ. While we attempt to facilitate access only to those Third Party Services that share our respect for your privacy, we cannot take responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those Third Party Services. 

In connection with your use of Sulia, we receive information about you from various sources, including: (i) through your Sulia user account (your “Account”); (ii) your use of Sulia generally; and (iii) from Third Party Services to which you elect to connect. When you use Sulia, you are consenting to the collection, transfer, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

## Information Collected and Used by Sulia.

The information we gather enables us to personalize, improve and operate Sulia. We collect and use the following types of information from our users. 

**Sign-In Information:**

When you create an Account with Sulia, you will provide information that could include Personally Identifiable Information, such as your username, password and email address. This information may be personal to you, and by creating an Account with Sulia and providing Personally Identifiable Information to us, you allow others, including us, to identify you through the information on your profile page. We may use your contact information to send you information about Sulia. You may unsubscribe from most of these messages through your Account settings, although we regardless reserve the right to contact you when we believe it is necessary, such as for account recovery purposes. 

**User Content:**

Sulia is a public forum, where users can share information and interact about topics of interest; therefore, most of the information posted through Sulia is public by default. 

We allow you to submit content to Sulia, such as the ability to create, curate, and distribute collections of content and uniform resource locators (“URLs”), written descriptions of content or URLs, comments, text, images and video. As a feature of Sulia, we collect and store that information. 

Personally Identifiable Information, such as your username and avatar, will potentially be included along with what you post and share but only to the extent that you decide to post. 

**IP Address Information and Other Information Collected Automatically:**

We gather information from the Sulia application or your web browser when you interact with Sulia, such as (i) the IP address and physical location of the devices accessing Sulia; (ii) the time and date of each access; and (iii) information about sharing of content. While we collect and store this information, it is not made public. We do at times, however, share some of this information with our partners, service providers and other persons with whom we conduct business, but such information cannot feasibly be linked to you individually. 

**Information Collected Using Cookies:**

Sulia takes your privacy very seriously.  We use cookies in industry standard ways to improve your experience and to improve our business.   Please read on for details. 

  * Cookies are pieces of text that may be provided to your computer through your web browser or application when you access a website or service. Your browser stores cookies in a manner associated with each website or service you visit. We use cookies to enable our servers to recognize your web browser or Sulia application and tell us how and when you visit and use Sulia through the web or through an application. 
  * While Sulia uses cookies to recognize you, it is our policy to never provide any Personally Identifiable Information obtained from these cookies to Third Party Services. 
  * Most browsers have an option for turning off the cookie feature, which will prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, as well as (depending on the sophistication of your browser software) allowing you to decide on acceptance of each new cookie in a variety of ways. If you disable cookies you may not be able to take advantage of the most attractive features of Sulia. 

**Information Related to Advertising:**

We may serve advertisements, and also allow third party advertisements, through Sulia. Advertisements served through Sulia may be targeted to users who fit a certain generic profile. Some of these advertisements may come from third party companies called “ad networks.”  Ad networks include third party ad servers, ad agencies, ad technology vendors and research firms. We do not provide Personally Identifiable Information to any ad networks for use outside of Sulia. 

**Aggregate Information:**

We collect statistical information about how people use Sulia (“Aggregate Information”). This statistical information is not Personally Identifiable Information and cannot be tied back to you, your Account, your web browser or your Sulia application. 

We share Aggregate Information with our partners, service providers and other persons with whom we conduct business. We share this type of statistical data so that our partners can understand how and how often people use Sulia and their services or websites, which facilitates improving both their services and how we interface with them. In addition, these third parties may share with us non-private, aggregated or otherwise non Personally Identifiable Information about you that they have independently developed or acquired. 

## How and To Whom Is My Information Shared?

Sulia is designed to help you share information that you or people you choose to follow elect to post to Sulia or Third Party Services. 

**Public Sulia Activity Information:**

Much of your activity on and through Sulia is public by default. This includes, but is not limited to: 

  * Channels and members that you follow, your profile information, including selected avatar/image, user name, bio, etc.
  * Content that you create and curate on your Account, and metrics and analytics information for your curated content, as described above. 

Some of this information may be associated with your Account and some of this information is publicly accessible to other Sulia users who choose to follow your curated content. Therefore, we urge you to think carefully about including any specific information you may deem private in content that you create or submit through Sulia. 

Any information that you elect to make public through Sulia will be instantly distributed and may then become accessible to users of Sulia, Third Party Services to which we distribute content, and Third Party Services that you link to Sulia. Sulia respects the privacy settings/policies that you have selected with Third Party Services, and only shares information consistent with those privacy settings and policies. 

**Information Shared with Our Agents:**

We employ and contract with people and other entities that perform certain tasks on our behalf and who are under our control (our “Agents”). We may need to share Personally Identifiable Information with our Agents in order to provide products or services to you. Our Agents do not have any right to use Personally Identifiable Information or other information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. 

**Information Disclosed Pursuant to Business Transfers:**

In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the transferred business assets. Moreover, if we, or substantially all of our assets associated with Sulia, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that may be transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of us may continue to use your Personally Identifiable Information as set forth in this policy. 

**Information Disclosed for the Protection of Us and Others:**

We also reserve the right to access, read, preserve, and disclose any information as we reasonably believe is necessary to (i) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, (ii) enforce these Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations hereof, (iii) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, (iv) respond to user support requests, or (v) protect our rights, property or safety, our users and the public. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and spam prevention. 

**Information We Share With Your Consent:**

Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Personally Identifiable Information may be shared with third parties, and will be able to prevent the sharing of this information. 

## How Can I Delete My Account?

Should you ever decide to delete your Account, you may do so by emailing [support@sulia.com](mailto:support@sulia.com). If you terminate and delete your Account, any association between your Account and information stored in connection with Sulia will no longer be accessible. However, you understand that (i) certain User Content will remain available, (ii) any of your User Content that has been re-posted will not be removed and will continue to be used in accordance with the Terms of Use, and (iii) any removed User Content may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time. 

## What Happens When There Are Changes to this Privacy Policy?

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we collect or use information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on or within Sulia or sending you an email. A user is bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses Sulia after such changes have been first posted. 

## What If I Have Questions or Concerns?

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy using Sulia, please send us a detailed message to [privacy@sulia.com](mailto:privacy@sulia.com). We will make every effort to resolve your concerns. 

Effective Date: October, 2011.
